Damjan Pjević,

a student at the School of Economics and Business

Contact damjan@pjevic.com Online presence www.pjevic.com linkedin.com/in/pjevic

PERSONAL STATEMENT

An ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused on Digital Communication, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in Business Informatics at the School of Economics and Business in Ljubljana. Experienced with working with the clients, public speaking and working in a team and with a working history in the fields of the computer software industry, event organisation, digital media and marketing.

SKILLS

ΙT Website management, mobile

application development, basics

in telecommuniations.

Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML & Programming

CSS, WordPress.

Marketing & PR Content creation, verbal

communication, promotional events.

Languages Slovenian C2, English C2, Serbian

B2, German B1, Russian A1.

EXPERIENCES

Epicoro [2021-now]

Wordpress developer

- · Building basic and intermediate websites using Elementor and Wordpress for various local companies.
- · Restructuring processes using Click-Up and Airtable.
- Helping out with photography, video editing and live streaming.

Technical Assistant

Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia [2019 - 2021]

- Independently overseeing technical aspect and providing support for online events with around 10 speakers and more than 100 participants carried out in English or Slovenian.
- · Recorded and edited over 50 videos (presentations and reportages) for

various events.

Website manager & Content creator

Value Add Games [2019-2020]

- Helped in marketing with the launch
- of their most successful product.
- Re-established the online shop.
- · Maintained the website and the online shop.

EDUCATION

2020-2022 Business Informatics - Masters. School of Economics and Business. University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

2015-2019 Multimedia Engineering - Bachelors.

Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)

Selected class projects

- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile **Emergency Application with extended** reality.
- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.

Extracurriculars:

[2019] Took part in the BEST Summer Course in Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and

how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its success.

[2016-2019] Took part in various promotional

events of the faculty.

[2012-2015] Took part in three different YouthPass

exchanges all focused on international

Peer-to-Peer communication.

[2011-2015] High School Debate club.

AWARDS

[2017] Reached top 20 out of 350 global

teams in OnePlus Student Marketing

Challenge.

[2016] Regional winners in global competition

OSCE.

Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool for challenging violent extremism.